Elsayed Ashrf Ashour



Contact

Address:

Mansoura, Egypt

Phone:

- +201093152235
- +201154382289

Email:

ssayedaashrf@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/sayed -ashrf-ba90861a6/

GitHub:

https://github.com/eng-sayed

Languages

Arabic – Native English – A2

Summary

An ambitious and proactive Flutter developer, I have more than two years of experience in the field of mobile application development and have dealt with a lot of technology such as Hive , Firebase, Pusher, Rest API, etc .I try to be a better version of myself Every day, by targeting different types of companies, I try to improve my education and Knowledge by participating in online sessions have space to allow Continuous self-motivation and development.

Skill Highlights

- Dart
- Flutter
- OOP
- Firebase
- FCM
- Agora
- Pusher
- Rest API
- Microsoft Office

- Hive
- Saflite
- State Management (Provider, Getx, Cubit)
- Design Pattern (MVC, MVVM)
- Code Push (shorebird)
- CICD (codemagic)
- Payment gateway (hyperpay – my fatorah-)

Experience

Mobile Application Developer - Almasader Alraqmia,

Mansoura
Part time (Sept 2023 - Feb 2024)
Full time (Feb 2024 - Now)

- Flutter Developer Neop, Mansoura Full time (Feb 2023 Feb 2024)
- Flutter Developer ProMina Agency, Cairo
 Full time (Sep 2022 Jan 2023)
- Mobile Application Developer Reeras Technologies, Mansoura
 Full time (Jan 2020 - Jul 2022)
 Part time (Jan 2024 - Now)

Education

Bachelor of Engineering: **Electronics & Communications** Sep 2017 – Jun 2022

Mansoura Higher Institute of Engineering

Fehres App

Displaying e-books and modifying the display method to suit the user, adding subscriptions to the application to display books or displaying free samples, dividing books according to sections and authors.

• Eagles (App, Desktop) 🔹 🕨

A special application for learning investing and trading, starting your professional life, and increasing your profits. It contains two versions for phone and desktop. The application is secured from all hacking methods, screen recordings, recording the screen or running it on the emulator, and other features.

- Aziz Driver App property investment App specializing in off-plan and newly built properties in the UK, and user can enquire with agent about building by chating, call or video call
- Aziz Rider App Property investment App specializing in off-plan and newly built properties in the UK, and user can enquire with agent about building by chating, call or video call
- Haieen App property investment App specializing in off-plan and newly built properties in the UK, and user can enquire with agent about building by chating, call or video call
- Ovata App property investment App specializing in off-plan and newly built properties in the UK, and user can enquire with agent about building by chating, call or video call
- Ovata Agent App to help agent to communicate with client to help in enquiry units and show their Buildings
- Lavida A special application for a pharmaceutical company to track the locations of delegates and follow up on their progress and the deals they submitted to the company.
- Wasselle-Driver-App >
 App to help agent to communicate with client to help in enquiry units and show their Buildings
- Wasselle-Trader App
 App to help agent to communicate with client to help in enquiry units and show their Buildings
- Pertoot **É**

An application for displaying natural photos and videos of all qualities and uploading them within the application to be shown to others and purchased

Shareet-User App \$\blue{\pi}\$

An application to display your projects and search for someone who can work with you. Communication takes place between the client and the service provider using conversations to complete the work

• Shareet-Freelancers App **É**

An application for easy access to independent projects, applying for them, and earning money. Communication takes place between the client and the service provider using conversations to complete the work.

• Mozn 🗯 🕨

An application for displaying prayer times and displaying the call to prayer at the designated times. It contains an Istaghafar counter and religious supplications.

Civi-Line APP

A platform specialized in domestic labor services, organizing between labor offices and workers, providing work for new workers, and providing workers for other users.

• Elzagel App 🗳 🕨

A platform specialized in facilitating the process of sending and receiving gifts between users and providing more than one payment method, such as bank payment, upon receipt, or using a payment gateway, with the ability for the gift seller to communicate with individuals using chats.

- Lampa Tronics App
 Electronic Store in Egypt to help user explore and explore and order electronic component online
- 3food App
 Three Food Market to To order your nutritional needs of fruits, vegetables and others
- Supa Koto Mobile App Supa Koto app for Supa Koto auto painting in Egypt and request and book services for car maintenance, cleaning, comprehensive inspection, and car protection films.
- Dressy App
 Dressy is a App to resnt and buy dresses from the most famous brands